<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on theoretical background, case study and practical assignment</title><link>https://athenagraz.github.io/Cos20/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on theoretical background, case study and practical assignment</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-en</language><copyright>Meike Freya Chris Rosa Sophie Athena</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 20:23:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://athenagraz.github.io/Cos20/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTML for Content Strategists: Why it is important to communicate with programmers at eye level</title><link>https://athenagraz.github.io/Cos20/posts/heinz/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 20:23:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://athenagraz.github.io/Cos20/posts/heinz/</guid><description>Heinz Wittenbrink suggests in his lecture to get to grips with the basics of coding - content people need to understand how programming works at its core.
Black screens on which many small white, green, yellow or red characters flicker. Numbers, angle brackets, commas are displayed. For many, it is a big question mark what exactly programmers and software developers have in front of them when they are writing code. Most of the time it is shyness or perplexity that prevents one from asking more questions.</description></item><item><title>Static or dynamic web pages on the net: What the differences are and what advantages which system brings</title><link>https://athenagraz.github.io/Cos20/posts/takashi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 20:23:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://athenagraz.github.io/Cos20/posts/takashi/</guid><description>In his lecture, Takashi Linzbichler shows the advantages of programmes like Hugo. Why you save time during development and for which group of people they are ideal.
1.1 Difference between static and dynamic websites? A static website does not use an external database and is written in HTML and coded with CSS. Every website visitor will receive the same information. There is no other software needed to create a static website.</description></item></channel></rss>